

TAM PHAN Graphic Designer

"Today different from yesterday."





SUMARY

I love everything about graphic design, user interface and user experience.

I have 6 years experience in Graphic Design and UI/UX Design. For Graphic Design, I experienced in Corporate Identity Program (CIP), Package Design, Catalogues, Brochure, Leaflet and Online Advertising. For UI/UX Design, I experienced in mobile, website and native app.

EXPERIENCE

Gia Kien Mobile Co., LTD Graphic Design & SEO	2010 - 2011
Recess Co., LTD Photo Retouching Intern	2012
Le Bao Minh JSC Graphic - UI/UX Designer	2013 - 2016
VMB Nam Phuong Co., LTD Graphic - UI/UX Designer	2013 - 2016
Freelance Graphic - UI/UX Designer	2017 - present

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Infomation Technology Lotus University	2006 - 2009
Bachelor of Management Information System Ho Chi Minh University of Economic	2010 - 2012
Certificate of Graphic Design Pro Polygon Academy of Design	2010 - 2012
Certificate of Web Design University Of Science	2012

SKILLS Graphic Design UI/UX Design Photography HTML/CSS Video Editing Handrawn Self-studies SOFTWARES Photoshop Illustrator Indesign

XD

Figma

Premiere

Invision

REFERENCE

Dreamweaver

Sketch

QUAN CHÍ LƯƠNG Team Leader

Phone: 0907410882

Email: guanliang88@gmail.com

